{
    "id": "37f287cac3694164adefbaf5bf2f7e39",
    "title": "Passive verb forms exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "138ea855d5cf411ca7f10873a52c096b",
            "title": "Passive Verb Forms Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The work …………………. by my brother.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "completed",
                        "has completed",
                        "was completed",
                        "had completed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The match ………………… by our team.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may won",
                        "may be won",
                        "has won"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let the weak not …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "insulted",
                        "be insulted",
                        "is insulted",
                        "has insulted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The patient ……………………… by the nurse.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is looking after",
                        "is being looked after",
                        "has been looking after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The sparrows …………………… by the boy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "were feeding",
                        "were being fed",
                        "have fed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The enemy troupes ………………….. by our army.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have defeated",
                        "was defeating",
                        "have been defeated",
                        "has been defeated"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………… a chair by the officer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "offered",
                        "have offered",
                        "was offered"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ………………… to disclose your sources of income.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are requesting",
                        "have been requesting",
                        "are requested"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let the door …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "open",
                        "be opening",
                        "be opened"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let this rubbish …………………… .. away.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has thrown",
                        "is thrown",
                        "be thrown"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}